OK, I'm going to tell you a little bit about how
a very small team, it was three people for most
of the development, built Cloud Design in about 10 weeks
from idea to launching the product.
And the reason I'm going to share these things with you
is because the most common question I get asked
is, why did you decide to start working on this?
How did you see that this was an opportunity for building
a new AI-enabled product?
How'd you build it?
How'd you launch it?
So everything I'm going to cover here,
there is no real secret sauce.
These are all things that work well for us.
Take what you like.
You can do a lot of these things tomorrow.
To start, I want to tell you about what Anthropic Labs is.
It's kind of funny.
It's a lab inside a frontier lab.
We don't have any labs within Anthropic Labs,
but it is labs quite a ways down.
The way that we usually talk about it is as a bet factory.
And by that, I mean we have very small teams exploring
the frontier of what the models can do
and making bets about whether or not something will work.
We run experiments to find out what works.
We double down on the things that are working.
We fold the things that are not working.
And at any given time, we might have a dozen small teams
exploring different concepts.
So it's lots of exploration, small number
of really high conviction releases of things
that we think can be moonshots or change how
people work with the models.
There's a few products that came from here that you may know.
Cloud Code came out of labs.